Error_ImportVer1Running=Unable to import settings from running SAI Ver.1. Please close SAI Ver.1.
Import_Title=PaintTool SAI Ver.2 - Import Settings from Older Version
ImportCap_Anounce=About Change of Settings Store Folder
ImportTxt_Anounce=From SAI Ver.2 Preview.2020-01-07 version, the store destination of the program settings has been changed to the following folder. Also, brush forms and textures have been changed to be stored in this folder.
ImportTxt_NewFolder=<Documents>\\SYSTEMAX Software Development\\SAIv2
ImportRem_NewFolder=This import dialog is displayed if older version(s) of SAI is detected and the above folder does not exist, when SAI Ver.2 is started. If you delete the above folder and start SAI Ver.2, this dialog will be displayed again.
ImportCap_Import=Import Settings
ImportTxt_Import=Older version(s) of SAI is detected. Do you want to import the settings?
ImportCtl_NotImport=Do Not Import Settins
ImportCtl_FromVer1=Import Settings from SAI Ver.1 (Ver.1.0.2 or later)
ImportCtl_FromVer2=Import Settings from SAI Ver.2 Preview.2015-04-24 to 2019-08-12
ImportTxt_Path=Installation Path of SAI to Import Settings : 
ImportBtn_Path=...
ImportRem_Path=If import from SAI Ver.2, the brush forms and textures will not be imported if this field is blank.
ImportCtl_Ver1Like=Revert the behaviors and operations changed in update of Ver.2 from Ver.1 as much as possible.
ImportRem_Ver1Like=If this was specified, set automatically some settings related to differences in behavior and operation from Ver.1 in [Preference] page in [Options] dialog. Please Keep in mind that the changes intended to improve will also be invalidated.
Import_DirBoxV1=Please select the installation folder of SAI Ver.1 to import settings.
Import_DirBoxV2=Please select the installation folder of SAI Ver.2 to import settings.
