Option_Title=Options
OptCat_Tablet=Pen Tablet
OptCat_Keyboard=Keyboard Operation
OptCat_History=History and Recovery
OptCat_Environment=Environment
OptCat_Preference=Preference
OptTabCap_ApiSel=Pen Tablet Control API
OptTabDsc_ApiSel=Please select an API for pen tablet control. The bolded label is the current API. The change of API requires restarting SAI.
OptTabCtl_UseWinTab=Use WinTab API
OptTabRem_UseWinTab=This mode does not support Microsoft WinTab Driver.
OptTabCtl_UseV1Compat=Use WinTab API with Ver.1 Compatible Method
OptTabRem_UseV1Compat=This mode does not support Microsoft WinTab Driver.
OptTabCtl_UseWindowsApi=Use Windows API
OptTabRem_UseWindowsApi=On Windows Vista and 7, this mode uses TabletPC API. On Windows 8 or later, this mode uses WM_POINTER messages. The pressure resolution is suppressed to 1024 levels for WM_POINTER messages, though 1024 levels is enough for actual drawings and paintings.
OptTabCap_PosMode=Coordinate Control Mode (Mainly For Wacom Tablet)
OptTabDsc_PosMode=The mouse mode setting in the tablet driver is always ignored on SAI. If you want to use pen as like mouse in SAI, please set it here.
OptTabCtl_AbsMode=Pen Mode
OptTabCtl_RelMode=Mouse Mode
OptTabTxt_RelSpeed=Move Speed : 
OptTabCap_MinPrs=Minimum Pressure for Brush Stroke
OptTabTXT_MinPrs=Minimum Pressure : 
OptTabRem_MinPrs=This value suppresses the sensitiveness of the pen pressure rising. And this value is applied to the click detection in Ver.1 compatible WinTab mode.
OptKeyCap_Shift=Shift Behavior for Selection of Tools and Functions
OptKeyDsc_Shift=The definition of Shift-Behavior is temporary selecting of an item while the shortcut key of the item is held down.
OptKeyCtl_TsEnable=Enable shift behavior for tool selecting
OptKeyCtl_GsEnable=Enable shift behavior for tool group selecting
OptKeyCtl_ForceXs=Start shift behavior before the detection when a drag is started
OptKeyTxt_XsTime=Shift Behavior Detection Period : 
OptKeyUnt_XsTime= msec
OptKeyCap_Toggle=Toggle Behavior for Selection of Tools and Tool Groups
OptKeyCtl_TtEnable=Undo the tool selection with a same shortcut key pressing
OptKeyCtl_GtEnable=Undo the tool group selection with a same shortcut key pressing
OptKeyCap_SupModKey=Suppression of Accidental Operation
OptKeyTxt_SupModKey=Duration for suppression of modifier keys after using of [Modkey + Key] : 
OptKeyUnt_SupModKey= msec
OptKeyRem_SupModKey=This setting is existing mainly to suppress a brush stroke(Drag) becomes a layer move(Ctrl+Drag) accidently immediately after the undo shortcut(Ctrl+Z).
OptHisCap_HisRecov=History and Recovery
OptHisCtl_EvacHisData=To suppress memory usage, evacuate history data to the local disk from main memory
OptHisRem_EvacHisData=This setting is enabled from the next created/opened canvas.
OptHisCtl_KeepHis=To recover works from a crash etc., keep recovery points and histories until the expiry
OptHisRem_KeepHis=This setting is enabled from the next created/opened canvas.
OptHisCtl_RecovHis=Recover the history when opened a SAI2 file if the history of the save timing is keeping
OptHisRem_RecovHis=If the last saved file type for a work is a SAI2 file, the history is linked to the SAI2 file and kept without an expiry. However the link will be lost if the SAI2 file is overwrote, renamed, moved or deleted.
OptHisCtl_KeepPeriod=The keeping period of recovery point and history that unlinked from SAI2 file : 
OptHisUnt_KeepPeriod= hours
OptHisRem_KeepPeriod=The deletion of expired recovery points and histories is executed when closing app. If specified 0, the deletion is not executed.
OptEnvCap_Performance=Countermeasure when Program is Poor Responsivity
OptEnvDsc_Performance=If the responsiveness of SAI is poor, such as when brush strokes are delayed, it may be improved by changing the settings below. The change of [CPU Assignment] requires restarting SAI.
OptEnvTxt_CpuAssignment=CPU Cores Assignment : 
OptEnvCtl_CpuAssignBetter=A. Allocate all CPU cores with an emphasis on processing speed
OptEnvCtl_CpuAssignReduce=B. Decrease the number of CPU cores used and allocate with an emphasis on responsiveness
OptEnvRem_CpuAssignment=If the responsiveness of SAI is poor, please try the option B and decrease [Number of CPU Cores Used] by 1 or 2.
OptEnvTxt_ReduceCores=Number of CPU Cores Used : 
OptEnvUnt_ReduceCores= Cores
OptEnvTxt_Priority=Process Priority : 
OptEnvCtl_PriorNormal=Normal (Default)
OptEnvCtl_PriorAbove=Above Normal
OptEnvCtl_PriorHigh=High
OptEnvRem_Performance=* Please note that even if the above settings improve responsiveness, it is not a fundamental solution. To determine the cause of poor responsiveness, first check the [CPU] in [Performance] tab in [More Details] mode of Task Manager. If the CPU usage remains above 3-4% even though there is no constant load such as video player or update process such as Windows Update, some program is constantly using CPUs unnecessarily. In that case, find the program that is constantly using CPUs in the list of processes in Task Manager and stop or uninstall it.
OptEnvCap_Paths=The Store Location of History/Recovery Data and Image File Thumbnails
OptEnvDsc_Paths=Please input a path in a local drive. The change of the store location is aplied from the next starting of SAI. The stored contents is moved at the next starting.\n* The change of the store location is not applied for Ver.2017-07-29 or earlier. And the stored contents is not moved on Ver.2019-01-29 or earlier.
OptEnvTxt_PathCurUsrLoc=Current Location : 
OptEnvTxt_PathNewUsrLoc=New Location : 
OptPrfCap_Common=Common
OptPrfCmCtl_UseAltSpc=Show the system menu with Alt + Space
OptPrfCmCtl_NoDblClk=Disable the operation to open a property of an item by double click
OptPrfCmCtl_DispFsysPath=Display file system path instead of shell namespace path
OptPrfCmRem_DispFsysPath=Display a path like 'C:\\folder\\file.sai2' instead of like 'Local Disk(C:) / folder / file.sai2'.
OptPrfCmCtl_DontHideSepPanels=Do not hide separated panels when turned off [Show All User Interface Panels]
OptPrfCap_FileViewer=FileViewer
OptPrfFvCtl_UseFilesysApi=Browse files and folders using only the file system API
OptPrfFvRem_UseFilesysApi=To access remote computers with this setting enabled, need to create a network drive.
OptPrfFvCtl_KeepLastPathOpen=Always open the last selected path for [Open]
OptPrfFvCtl_KeepLastPathExpo=Always open the last selected path for [Export]
OptPrfCap_Canvas=Canvas
OptPrfCvTxt_SaveEndWait=The wait time before hiding the progress bar after canvas saving is complete : 
OptPrfCvUnt_SaveEndWait= msec
OptPrfCap_Layer=Layer
OptPrfLyCtl_ShowPsBlendName=For layer blending modes, use common names instead of SAI dialect
OptPrfLyCtl_ShowTslBlendMode=Add 'The 8 Special Blending Modes' allowed 'Transparency Shapes Layer' into the blend mode dropdown list
OptPrfLyRem_ShowTslBlendMode=Linear Burn, Linear Doudge, Linear Light, Color Burn, Color Doudge, Vivid Light, Hard Mix and Difference are called 'The 8 Special Blending Modes'. The blending results of 'The 8 Special Blending Modes' are different by 'Transparency Shapes Layer' checkbox in Photoshop.
OptPrfLyCtl_AllowInvisProc=Allow processing of invisible layers
OptPrfLyRem_AllowInvisProc=This setting is applied to Cut, Move, Transformation, Rasterization and Color Adjustment.
OptPrfLyCtl_MergeClipNext=Merge the parent layer of a clipping group to the next layer without merging the group
OptPrfCap_View=View
OptPrfVwCtl_FitToWindow=Fit the view scale to the window when reset the position of a view
OptPrfVwCtl_WheelInv=Swap zoom-in and zoom-out for mouse wheel on view
OptPrfVwCtl_WheelVCen=Zoom in or out by mouse wheel at the center of view always
OptPrfVwCtl_Ver1Margin=Expand the scroll range of view to the same as Ver.1
OptPrfVwTxt_MinMargin=Minimum width outside of an image when reset the position of a view : 
OptPrfCap_Navigator=Navigator
OptPrfNvCtl_HideIndicator=Hide the indicator of canvas position in not operating navigator
OptPrfCap_Color=Color
OptPrfCoCtl_Hsv255=Change the value scale of HSV/HSL sliders from 0-100 to 0-255 same as Ver.1
OptPrfCap_Brush=Brush Tools
OptPrfBrCtl_V1Fealing=Adjust the feeling of brush stroke end in stabilizer 1-15 to similar to Ver.1
OptPrfBrRem_V1Fealing=If the tablet control mode is [Windows API],  the drawing will be aborted immediately when the pen upped outside of the view window. This setting is able to override by [Stabi. Mode] in [Miscellaneous] of a brush tool.
OptPrfBrCtl_DelayCircle=Put the brush circle at stabilized coordinate
OptPrfBrCtl_TrueSizeCircle=Display the brush circle in the true painting size
OptPrfBrCtl_RelSizeChg=Change brush size relatively with [Ctrl + Alt + Drag]
OptErr_UsrLocNotLocal=[The Store Location of History Data and Image File Thumbnails] in [Environment] page is not a path in a local drive.
